The End is a drama, music film directed by Joshua Oppenheimer.
Twenty-five years after environmental collapse left the Earth uninhabitable, Mother, Father and Son are confined to their palatial bunker, where they struggle to
maintain hope and a sense of normalcy by clinging to the rituals of daily life—until the arrival of a stranger, Girl, upends their happy routine.
As tensions rise, their seemingly idyllic existence starts to crumble.
Mother, played by Tilda Swinton.
Son, played by George MacKay.
Girl, played by Moses Ingram.
Father, played by Michael Shannon.
Friend, played by Bronagh Gallagher.
Butler, played by Tim McInnerny.
The End is a 2024 apocalyptic musical film directed
and co-written by Joshua Oppenheimer.
Produced by Oppenheimer, Signe Byrge Sørensen, and star Tilda Swinton, the film also features George
MacKay, Moses Ingram, Bronagh Gallagher, Tim McInnerny, Lennie James, and Michael Shannon.
The story follows a wealthy family living in an underground bunker, after a global environmental
disaster leaves Earth inhospitable, whose dynamics alter following the arrival of a survivor.
The End premiered at the 51st Telluride Film Festival on 31 August 2024.
It was released by Neon in the United States on 6 December 2024.
The film received a mixed reception from critics.
The film explores themes of bunker, post-apocalyptic future, musical.
The tone is emotional.